Beelzebubs Records UA238
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Beelzebubs Records
2002 -- 2020
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Beelzebubs
UA238
32 Digital Object(s) 32 digital objects comprising 159 files.
2 Web sites
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into three series: Web crawls; Albums; and Trips.
Biographical / Historical
Beelzebubs is an all-male a capella group that was founded at Tufts University in 1963 by Bill Amidon, Don Avery, Barrie Bruce, and Neal Robison.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains records and web crawls from the Tufts University all-male a capella group the Beelzebubs. Materials include two of their albums, Punch and Shedding, and videos and photographs from their 2006 trip to Greece.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research. This collection may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
Student life; Student Activities -- Student Government, Clubs, and Organizations; Student Activities -- Performing Arts
- Web crawls, 2015 -- 2020; UA238.001; 2 Web sites
  Scope and Contents
  Quarterly web crawls of the Tufts Beelzebubs websites crawled by DCA, as part of the Student Organizations web collection, to document the presesence of Tufts University student organizations on the web.
  Other Finding Aids
  To see all of websites crawled as part of the Student Organizations web collection, please visit https://archive-it.org/collections/6387
  - Beelzebubs, 2015 -- 2020; UA238.001.00001
    Conditions Governing Access
    Open for research.
    General
    Frequency: quarterly crawl.
  - Beelzebubs - Twitter, 2015 -- 2020; UA238.001.00002; Beelzebubs
- Albums, 2002 -- 2005; UA238.000010; 99.6 Megabytes; 29 Digital Object(s)
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Transferred by the Office of the President, 2007, accession 2008.024.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically by album.
  This series contains the Beelzebubs albums "Punch" and "Shedding."
  - Punch, 2002; UA238.000011; 44.1 Megabytes; 14 Digital Object(s)
    - Elevation, 2002; UA238.000012; 3.11 Megabytes
    - Space Between, 2002; UA238.000013; 3.75 Megabytes
    - Falling in Love, 2002; UA238.000014; 4.11 Megabytes
    - Who Put the Bomp, 2002; UA238.000015; 2.5 Megabytes
    - Rockin' Robin, 2002; UA238.000016; 2.01 Megabytes
    - Made a Woman, 2002; UA238.000017; 2.72 Megabytes
    - Duke of Earl, 2002; UA238.000018; 2.56 Megabytes
    - More Love, 2002; UA238.000019; 2.59 Megabytes
    - How Can I Move On, 2002; UA238.000020; 2.67 Megabytes
    - Pretty Momma, 2002; UA238.000021; 3.49 Megabytes
    - No Sunshine When She Gone, 2002; UA238.000022; 3.09 Megabytes
    - In the End, 2002; UA238.000023; 3.35 Megabytes
    - Carry the Weight, 2002; UA238.000024; 6.51 Megabytes
    - Brothers in Song, 2002; UA238.000025; 1.68 Megabytes
  - Shedding, 2005; UA238.000026; 55.5 Megabytes; 15 Digital Object(s)
    - Let's Get it Started, 2005; UA238.000027; 3.24 Megabytes
    - Better Days-Where It's At, 2005; UA238.000028; 3.68 Megabytes
    - Pony, 2005; UA238.000029; 3.08 Megabytes
    - Everybody Wants to Rule the World, 2005; UA238.000030; 2.86 Megabytes
    - Ladies' Night, 2005; UA238.000031; 2.78 Megabytes
    - Trouble, 2005; UA238.000032; 3.97 Megabytes
    - Someday I Suppose, 2005; UA238.000033; 2.66 Megabytes
    - Let's Go, 2005; UA238.000034; 3.11 Megabytes
    - Epiphany, 2005; UA238.000035; 3.9 Megabytes
    - The Distance, 2005; UA238.000036; 2.78 Megabytes
    - Heavy Things, 2005; UA238.000037; 2.95 Megabytes
    - Boulevard of Broken Dreams, 2005; UA238.000038; 3.93 Megabytes
    - Hurt, 2005; UA238.000039; 3.96 Megabytes
    - Paranoid Android, 2005; UA238.000040; 5.6 Megabytes
    - You Can't Always Get What You Want, 2005; UA238.000041; 7.01 Megabytes
- Trips, 2006 January; UA238.000042; 361.4 Megabytes; 3 Digital Object(s) 3 digital objects comprising 130 files.
  This series is arranged in the order in which it was received.
  This series contains photographs and videos from the Beelzebubs trip to Greece in 2006, including to the Acropolis and a children's hospital. Photographs and videos document the group's travels and performances.
  - Trip to Greece, 2006 January; UA238.000043; 361.4 Megabytes; 3 Digital Object(s) 3 digital objects comprising 130 files.
    - Bubs at hospital, 2006 January 14; UA238.000044; 179.9 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 61 files.
    - Beelzebubs in Greece, 2006 January 16; UA238.000045; 30.1 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 11 files.
    - Bubs at Acropolis, 2006 January 16; UA238.000046; 151.4 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 58 files.